

Muhammad Mahdi Dewantoro

+6285736013100 | mahdi9191@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/muhemde Probolinggo, East Java, 67282 23rd December 1995



About Me

A hard worker, highly motivated and professional offering more than 3 years experience in projects and variety of expertise such as human resources and administration. Engaging personality with strong desire to work hard in rigorous environments. I have career interest in the field of human resources or in other fields.

Skills

- Microsoft Office
- SIPP BPJS Ketenagakerjaan
- e-Dabu BPJS Kesehatan
- e-Faktur
- UU Ketenagakerjaan
- Legality and Company License
- Payroll
- Absenteeism

- Compensation and Benefit
- Administration
- Leadership
- Interpersonal
- Team Work
- Logical and Critical Thinking
- Initiative
- Fast Learner

Work History

- PT. Geo Core Samudra Indonesia

Construction Company, East Jakarta – DKI Jakarta Human Resource and General Affair (HRGA) Staff

03/2017 - 03/2020

- Did task such as correspondence, payroll, absenteeism, BPJS Ketenagakerjaan and Kesehatan, compensation and benefit, nomor induk berusaha (NIB), surat ijin usaha jasa konsruksi (SIUJK), surat badan usaha (SBU), SKA, notarial deed, building rent and Bill of Quantity (BoQ).
- Made company online and offline archives 75% more efficient.
- Dewatering Project Sahid Kuta Life Style and Resort 2 by PT. Tatamulia Nusantara Indah Kuta, Badung, Bali

Supervisor

10/2018 - 10/2019

- In charge of recruitment and training 8 manpower, project team meetings, deadline updates, project equipment and supplies, mobilization and demobilization, payroll, compensation and benefit, absenteeism, Bill of Quantity (BoQ), lodging and transportation.
- Slashed 20% manpower without reduced the quality of the performance and saved costs more than 25% while projects.
- Resolved conflicts and negotiated mutually beneficial agreements between parties (main contractor and sub-contractor).
- Resolved dewatering, project progress and manpower problems.
- Led with 0 (zero) accident.

- Dewatering Project Shangri-La Hotel and Resort Nusa Dua by PT. Tatamulia Nusantara Indah

Nusa Dua, South Kuta, Badung, Bali

Dewatering Project Supervisor

04/2016 - 02/2018

- In charge of recruitment and training 20 manpower, project team meetings, deadline updates, project equipment and supplies, mobilization and demobilization, payroll, compensation and benefit, absenteeism, lodging and transportation.
- Slashed 60% manpower without reduced the quality of the performance and saved cost more than 35% while projects.
- Resolved conflicts and negotiated mutually beneficial agreements between parties (main contractor and sub-contractor).
- Resolved dewatering, project progress and manpower problems.
- Led with 0 (zero) accident.

- PT. Taspen (Persero)

Insurance Company, Malang – East Java

Finance Internship

09/2016 - 12/2016

- Help created tax repots, costumer dues, KARIP, death insurance, DAMU, accountability reports (LPJ), and correspondences. 100% successful on this job although in the University focused on Human Resource Management.
- Analyzed data from 500+ users which is used to make payments and accountability reports.

- Dewatering Project POP! Hotel Tanjung Benoa

Tanjung Benoa, South Kuta, Badung, Bali Dewatering Project Administration

04/2015 - 09/2015

Liable for project equipment and supplies, mobilization and demobilization, absenteeism, compensation and benefit, payroll, lodging, transportation, project progress and correspondences.

Education

- Brawijaya University, Malang (2013 – 2018)

Bachelor Degree in the field of Business Administration focused on Human Resource Management Cumulative GPA 3.17/4.00

- 100 students selected to take a part in the "Sekolah Kebangsaan Brawijaya 2013" at 9th, 10th and 16th November 2013.
- Publication : Pengaruh Lingkungan Kerja dan Motivasi Kerja terhadap Prestasi Kerja Karyawan (Studi pada Karyawan Tetap Giant Ekstra Gajayana Malang).

- Tunas Luhur Paiton (2010 – 2013)

Social Science

Cumulative GPA 8.10/10.00

- "Kebangsaan" Speech Competiton Held by Paiton District Goverment (2012).
- Probolinggo Regency level selection of National Science Olympiad in the field of Economics (2012).
- Economic Olympics by Faculty of Economics and Business University of Jember (2011).

Organizational History

- (2014 2015) HRD staff at Student Entrepreneur Center Faculty of Administrative Science Brawijaya University, Malang.
- (2013 2014) Graphic designer staff at Student Entrepreneur Center Faculty of Administrative Science Brawijaya University, Malang.
- (2013) Sekolah Kebangsaan Brawijaya.
- (2010 2011) Graphic designer staff at Tunas Luhur Paiton Senior High School Pers.

Training/Course/Webinar

Paduan Payroll Sederhana Karva One

Administrasi HR untuk Pemula

6th November 2020

Karya One

26th October 2020

English For Adults

English First

South Jakarta, DKI Jakarta

Progress: Level 8 (Intermediate)

09/2019 - 09/2020

Languages

Bahasa Indonesia: Fluent

English : Intermediate

Certification

K3 Basic Factory by Reanata Consultant 2020 Akuntansi Dasar dan Keuangan Bisnis by Finata 2020 Microsoft Office Desktop Application by Trust Training Partners 2017